const grade2data=[
    {
        question:"accommodation",
        choices:["推薦","賞賛","結合","宿泊設備"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"classification",
        choices:["分類","明確化","正当化","多様化"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"destination",
        choices:["運命","指定","目的地","決定"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"foundation",
        choices:["資金","基礎","公式","形成"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"illusion",
        choices:["混乱","分散","幻覚","妄想"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"charge for",
        choices:["～を担当する","～に突進する","～を訴える","～を請求する"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"show off",
        choices:["現れる","案内する","見せびらかす","見送りする"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"take over",
        choices:["離陸する","騙す","引き継ぐ","似ている"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"make up for",
        choices:["～を理解する","～の埋め合わせをする","～に役立つ","～で間に合わせる"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"lay off",
        choices:["一時解雇する","計画する","非難する","備蓄する"],
        answer:0
    }
]

export default grade2data;